原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
翻译     累
校对     累
时间轴     西·查    想念Gallifrey的Wholock
后期     累
总监     累
你肯定醉的不轻  才会这么做
You must've been really drunk to do that.
做什么
Do what?
这个
This.
你为什么要这么做
Why in the hell would you do that?
说来话长
It's kind of a long story.
我有时间啊
I got time.
靠  我没有时间了
Oh, shit. No, I don't.
我得走了
Get moving.
拉勒米  我们
Laramie, let's...
不是吧
Seriously?
拉勒米  醒醒  迟到了
Laramie. Wake up. We're late.
走吧
Let's go.
今天你会感觉很漫长  罗伊德
Gonna be a long day, Lloyd.
毕竟你没怎么睡
Didn't get much sleep.
黄石
第三季  第十集[季终]
如果你想找寻这里的回忆
If you're looking for a connection to this place,
你是找不到的
you're not gonna find it.
这里是租的
This is just a rental.
我想找的不是回忆
It's not a connection to this place that I'm looking for.
我有兄弟姐妹  表亲吗
Do I have any brothers? Cousins? Sisters?
你想决定什么
What are you trying to decide?
我的家人
Who my family is.
那已经决定了
Well, that's already been decided.
你在东蒙大拿州有几个表亲
You got a couple cousins in east Montana
还有一个同父异母的兄弟
and a half brother somewhere...
你爷爷躲在法戈的一家疗养院
Your grandfather is holed up in a nursing home in Fargo.
那个混蛋快一百岁了
Bastard's nearly a hundred and he is living proof
他就是好人不长命的证明
that only the good die young.
还有我
And there's me.
你知道我的过去
You know what I am.
你妈妈
And your mother...
我记得我出门  开长途拉牛
I remember I'd been out long-hauling goddamn cattle.
我回家时
I came home,
发现你在尖叫
and I found you screaming...
因为你快饿死了
'cause you were fucking starving.
你拿着一个旧裂纹管
You had a hold of an old crack pipe
吮吸它的一端
and you were sucking on the tip of it
你以为它是乳头
like it was a nipple...
边叫边吸
in between screams.
我发现她弯腰趴在水池上
And I found her bent over the sink
被一个胖子
by some fat piece of shit...
我知道你只有一次机会
and I knew that you had only one chance
但你的人生中不能有她
in life, and that was without her in it.
所以我动手了
So, I did what I did...
我夺走了她的生命  放弃了我的生命
I took her life and gave up mine.
都是为了你
For you...
现在看着你  可以说这是我
Looking at you now, I would say that it was probably
当时最好的选择
the best choice I could've made.
虽然约翰·杜顿养大了你
John Dutton may have raised you,
但他爱过你吗  儿子
but did he love you, son?
他现在爱你吗
Does he love you now?
他爱的是牧场
He loves a goddamn ranch.
这就是他所爱的一切
That's all he's ever loved.
你站在我的院子  就说明你已经知道了
You standing in my yard tells me you already knew it.
你只剩我一个家人了  儿子
I'm your family, son. I'm the only one you got.
我为之奋斗的一切
Everything that I worked for.
我之前的身份
Everything that I thought I was...
都要没了
I'm going to lose.
我从小的目标就是经营那个牧场
I was raised to run that ranch.
我把它变成了今天的样子
I built it into what it is today.
那就经营吧
Then run it.
它不是我的
It's not mine.
那个牧场是非卖品  况且我也买不起
It's not for sale. Not that I could afford it.
没有人买得起黄石
Nobody can afford Yellowstone.
黄石不是一个牧场
Yellowstone ain't a ranch.
而是一个帝国  帝国是要靠抢的
It's an empire. Empires you take.
我不知道该怎么抢
I don't know how to do that.
这是地球上最简单的事情
Oh, it's the simplest thing on earth.
杀了国王
You kill the King.
我不会杀人
I'm not a killer.
你没杀过人吗
You've never killed?
你杀过人
Yeah, you've killed.
你已经杀过人了
Of course, you've killed.
你是兰德尔家的人
You're a Randall.
杀戮是我们唯一的天赋
And killing is our only gift.
抱歉
Sorry.
不用道歉
Don't be sorry.
这需要时间
It takes time.
现在我明白你的感受了
Guess I know what it feels like to be you now.
是啊  而且还不止一方面
Yeah. In more ways than one.
我们搬到牧场是为了和你在一起
You know, we moved to the ranch to be with you
可你现在都不在牧场待着了
and now you're never here.
这个牲畜委员会委员
This, uh... this livestock thing.
这是一份全职工作
It's a full time job.
你挺喜欢的吧
You like it, don't you?
我喜欢为了人去奋斗
I like having somebody to fight for.
而不是为了什么东西
Rather than some thing.
当你为一个东西奋斗时
When you fight for a thing,
它并不在乎输赢
the thing don't care if you win or lose
因为它没有生命
because the thing ain't alive.
但当你为人奋斗时  他们会在乎
But when you fight for people, they care.
是啊  这也是我喜欢的地方
Yeah, that's what I like about it, too.
但我觉得东西也会在乎  土地也会在乎
But I think a thing can care. I think the land cares.
我明白你的意思  宝贝
I know you do, baby.
这就是我爱你的地方
That's what I love about you.
我们真正关心的是
What we're really concerned
是高收益和杠杆贷款
with is high yield and leverage loans...
过去的25年里
Interest rates globally have been in secular decline
全球利率一直在下降
for the past 25-plus years...
请留言  我回头打给你
Leave me a message and I'll call you back.
就是看看你怎么样了
Just checking in with you
因为你一直没和我联系
'cause you haven't checked in with me.
你的办公室有个阳台
You know, your office has a balcony.
我可在阳台以看到停车场
From the balcony, I see the parking lot.
我在屋顶可以看到保留地
From the roof I see the reservation.
我更喜欢停车场
I like the view of the parking lot better.
你可以祈祷我们不是你的人  但我们是的
You know, you can wish we weren't your people, but we are.
这并不是我所祈祷的
That's not what I wish.
那你在祈祷什么  安吉拉
What do you wish, Angela?
我祈祷我可以回到过去
I wish I could go back in time
告诉我们的人卖掉所有的武器
and tell our people to sell every weapon they have.
马匹
Every horse.
然后拿着钱去纽约
Then take that money and go to New York
雇佣市里最大的律师事务所
and hire the biggest law firm in the city.
如果可以的话  我们就不用站在这里了
If I could do that, we wouldn't be standing here.
我们可以站在黄石的门口
We'd be standing at the gates of Yellowstone
依然称之为我们的家
and still calling it home.
我们还会站在那里的
We'll stand there again.
和你在一起就不可能
Not with you we won't.
所谓的道德根本不存在
There's no such thing as morality.
有人拥有土地  也有人失去土地
There's own the land and there's lose the land.
这就是评判的标准
That's all you'll be judged by.
过程不重要
Not how you do it.
胜利者是不会被追究"过程"的
Winners are never judged by "how".
那是给失败者留着的
They save that for the losers.
你一晚上都没回来
You had a long night.
是啊
Yeah.
谢谢  亲爱的
Thank you, sweetie.
你杀了谁
Who'd you kill?
别问我这种问题  贝丝
Don't ask me that, Beth.
你杀了谁
Who'd you kill?
我说什么来着
What did I just say?
我们不能再这样了
We don't get to do that anymore.
哪样
What's that?
秘密
Secrets.
不能再有秘密了
We don't get those.
有些事我必须去做
There's things I do,
还有一些事我必须去摆平
and then there's things that I got to get done.
这些事你肯定不想听
You don't want to know them.
这不是秘密  亲爱的  我是为了你好
It's not a secret, Darling. It's a favor.
有多少
How many?
够了
Enough.
有多少事
How many?
这个牧场很大  贝丝
It's a big ranch, Beth.
我们的敌人不会公平战斗  你知道的
And our enemies don't fight fair, you know that.
多少
How many?
说真的  我也不知道
I don't know. Honestly.
别假装你不知道我们是怎么战斗的
Don't pretend like you don't know how we fight.
我当然知道
Oh, I know how you fight...
我赞同尼采关于是非的思想
I subscribe to Nietzsche's thoughts on right and wrong.
他是一位德国哲学家
He was a German philosopher who died of syphilis
收留妓女之后死于梅毒
after he cornholed some prostitute,
所以生活模式没什么好追求的
so not exactly a life to model yours after,
但他关于对与错  善与恶的思想
but his thoughts on right and wrong, good and evil.
就是根本没有对错善恶
Which were: there's no such thing.
这点我是相信的
That, I believe.
我相信要全身心地去爱
I believe in loving with your whole soul
如果有人想杀死你的所爱  就格杀勿论
and destroying anything that wants to kill what you love.
仅此而已
That's it.
就这么简单
That's all there is.
我也相信这一点
I believe in the same thing.
我收回那句话
I take it back.
你可以保守这个秘密
You can keep this secret.
失陪了
Now if you'll excuse me...
我也要杀个人
I gotta kill someone, too.
准备好了吗
You ready for this?
他们惹错人了  老爸
They fucked with the wrong bull, daddy.
是的
Yes, they did.
再见
I'll see you there.
你想要的东西  我拿到了
That thing you wanted back. I got it.
要我放在什么地方吗
Want me to put it some place?
不  我不想要
Naw, I don't want it.
只是不想让他拥有
Just didn't want him to have it...
他不会再来拿回去了吧
He's not gonna come looking for it, is he?
不会  先生
No, sir.
那趟火车只朝一个方向前进
That train only runs in one direction.
你查到他背后的人了吗
You find out who was holding his leash?
是个叫罗尔克的家伙
It's a guy by the name of Roarke.
我不认识他
I don't know who he is.
罗尔克
Roarke.
要我打听一下吗
Want me to start asking around?
不需要
No. No need.
一般人丢了狗
When people lose their dogs
都会到处问有没有人见过它们
they ask everyone if they've seen them.
他很快就会出现了
He'll show up soon enough.
好的  先生  有什么需要就找我
Yes, sir. Let me know if you need anything.
怎么了
What?
嗯  终于看到一个计划成功了
Well, it's nice to see a plan work out for once.
你的计划真的成功了  爸
I guess your plan did work out, Dad.
嗯
Well...
不是我的计划
Not my plan. My...
可能是我的梦想吧  但这是你的计划
My dream, maybe, but... Your plan.
有一说一  这是你为我打造的计划
Your plan for me, if you want to get down to it.
好吧  有一说一
All right, well, if you want to get down to it,
如果这不是你的命运  我的计划根本就不重要
it don't matter what my plan was if it ain't your destiny.
我不相信命运
I don't believe in destiny.
也是
Yeah, right.
就算是你  也没那么天真
Even you aren't that naive.
爸
Hey, Dad.
过得开心点
Have a good day.
不可能  儿子
I won't, son.
我的好日子已经结束了
I believe I'm all out of those.
拉勒米  走吧
Come on, Laramie. Let's go.
来了
I'm coming.
-东西都收拾好了吗  -嗯
- You have everything? - Yeah.
-马匹装车了吗  -嗯
- Horses loaded? - Oh, yeah.
都准备好了
We're all set.
-怎么了  -没什么
- What? - Nothin.
怎么啦
What?
说吧  为什么
Go ahead, why?
这有点难以解释
It's kind of hard to explain.
可不嘛  我真是想不明白
Yeah, I'd think so. I can't make sense of it.
沃克也有一个
Walker has one, too.
他把屁眼印在胸前我都不在乎
But he could have his asshole on his chest and I wouldn't care.
他真是个好男人
That is one fine son of a bitch.
你知道烙印意味着什么吗
Do you know what a brand means?
-意味着我是某个东西的一部分  -并不是
- Means I'm a part of something. - No, that's not what it means.
东西打上烙印以后  万一丢了
You brand something so that if it gets lost
大家都知道它属于谁
everyone knows who it belongs to.
所以才要打上烙印
That's why you do it.
早上好
Good morning.
等人都到了以后  我就送你们进去
Once the entire party is here I will escort you in.
我可以保证  人都到了
The entire party is here, I assure you.
我们还在等州长
We're still waiting on the Governor.
怕不是在逗我
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
一大早就要摆点谱  是吗
Decided to start the day with a little theater, did you?
一点点
Just a little.
很高兴再次见到你
It's good to see you again.
-州长  -杰米
- Governor. - Jamie.
请坐
Please, have a seat.
我这里有咖啡  橙汁
There's coffee, some orange juice,
那边还有什锦糕点
and some assorted pastries over there
如果有人敢吃谷蛋白的话
for anyone willing to brave gluten.
我不怕谷蛋白
I, for one, am not afraid of gluten.
能给我弄一盘吗  再来点咖啡
Could you make me a plate, please, and some coffee?
我们就开门见山吧
Well, I say we just dive in.
海斯女士  你们愿意先开始吗
Mrs. Hayes, would your team like to start?
林务局的租赁合同已经拿到了
The forest service lease has been secured.
联邦航空局已经批准了机场和跑道计划
FAA has approved both the airport and runway plans.
航空公司已经同意提供资金
The airlines have agreed to finance the build
建造各自的航站楼
of their respective terminals.
零售商的租约也齐了
Our leases with retail vendors are in place,
这样我们就可以资助机场建设
which allows us to fund the airport build...
不需要州政府的资金  所以你选举需要公债的理由
...without using state funds, which negates your requirement
也就不成立了  因为我们不需要公债
to place the bond on the ballot, because we don't need the bond.
我们只要
We just need...
匿名指控市场股票总裁工作场所骚扰
海斯女士  有什么问题吗
Mrs. Hayes, is there an issue?
有问题吗  威拉
Problem, Willa?
舒服了吧  贱人
Take that you fucking bitch.
埃利斯
Ellis?
我出去一下
I need to step out for a moment.
罗尔克有权就我们的立场发表意见
Roarke has the authority to speak on our position.
哪个是罗尔克
Roarke. Which one is he?
是我
That's me.
见过我以后  你就永远不会忘记了
Once you put a name to this face, you will never forget it.
嗯  我不会忘记的
No, I don't believe I will.
这给州政府带来了
Now... What this provides the state
机场  机票销售  租车  酒店税
is the added tax revenue from the airport, from ticket sales,
燃油销售增加的税收
car rentals, hotel taxes, fuel sales...
而且都是零投入
and all with zero investment.
这是一种永久性的可再生资源
It's a perpetually renewable resource
而且不需要州政府出一分钱
that doesn't cost the state one dime.
接下来就与你有关了  达顿先生
Which brings us to you, Mr. Dutton.
最适合机场建设的土地在这里
The land most suitable to the airport build... is this tract.
如果你想从黄石买地
If you're discussing purchasing land from the Yellowstone,
就得和我讨论一下
you will need to discuss it with me.
其实是和我讨论
Actually, you have to discuss it with me.
我有土地委托书
I have power of attorney over the estate.
前提是土地在犹他州
If the estate were in Utah.
你是在那里提交文件的
That's where you filed the documents.
蒙大拿州不承认
The State of Montana does not recognize
其他州签发的委托书
power of attorney issued by other states.
土地在蒙大拿州
The land is in Montana.
但她的委托书在犹他州
But her authority is in Utah.
如果她是律师  她肯定知道
I mean, if she was an attorney, she would know that.
现在看来  我是黄石的法律代表
As it stands, I am the legal authority representing the Yellowstone,
我同意出售那块土地
and I approve the sale of that tract.
想得美
The hell you will.
我同意  因为如果我不同意  土地委员会就会没收
Yes, I will, because if I don't, the Land Commission
你只能拿到土地价值十分之一的价格
will condemn it and you will get paid one tenth of what it's worth.
还要损失数百万的律师费
And you will also lose millions on attorneys
因为我无法代表牧场
because I cannot represent the ranch
同时还得没收它
and condemn it at the same time.
那就不要没收
Then don't condemn it.
这不是我的选择  这是她的选择
It's not my choice. It's her choice.
这是你的选择
It's your choice?
你会怎么选  莉奈儿
What do you choose, Lynelle?
没得选了  约翰
There is no choice anymore, John.
只剩选项了
There are only options.
我能看看环境影响报告吗
Could I see the environmental impact report?
林业局的报告就在你手上
The forest service report is in your packet.
不是林业局的报告
Not the forest service report.
鱼类及野生动物管理局
The U.S. Fish and Wildlife report on the impact
关于机场建在河边的影响报告
of an airport beside the river
毕竟那条河供养我们最古老的国家公园
that feeds our oldest national park.
一号跑道旁边的那条河
The one flowing beside runway one, right there.
这是我们诉讼的基础
That will be the basis of our lawsuit,
以防有人好奇
in case anyone was curious.
到时候我们会提出集体诉讼
It will be a class action suit
因为它会影响当地的土地和公园的土地
because it impacts native land and park land.
我们会跟大黄石联盟的律师碰头
We'll meet with attorneys from the Greater Yellowstone Coalition,
塞拉俱乐部
Sierra Club, you know.
所有人都会去
All the gang will be there.
祝你好运
Best of luck.
我们十年都没猎狼了
We stopped wolf hunting for a fucking decade.
你觉得我们会怎么处理机场呢
What do you think we're going to do to an airport?
我们不需要运气  法庭上见
We don't need luck. See you in court.
这也是你的角度  约翰
That's your angle, too, John.
这对你的土地有什么影响
How does this impact your land?
加入我们的诉讼  一分钱也用不花
Join our suit. It won't cost you a cent.
你不需要聘请律师
You won't have to hire an attorney.
我们会帮你聘的
We'll do it for you.
保留地曲线救国
A little curve ball from the Reservation.
黄石牧场
那片土地是我的
That land is mine.
除了我  没人可以卖
And no one can sell it but me.
赶紧多说两句"那片土地是我的"
I'd say that as much as you can: "that land is mine".
说痛快了
Get it all out of your system.
宠物丢了吗  罗尔克
Lose your pets, Roarke?
你以为你赢了这场比赛
You think you're winning this game,
但你连规则都还不知道
you don't even know the goddamn rules.
别担心  我会教你的
But don't worry: I'm gonna teach them to you.
你不打招呼  也不说再见
You don't say hello, you don't say goodbye.
你没什么可说的吗  儿子
You got nothing to say to me, son?
他一直就没什么话可说  爸
He never has anything to say, Dad.
我有很多话要说  贝丝
Oh, I have plenty to say, Beth.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
那我洗耳恭听
Well, I'm all fucking ears.
不出所料
That's what I thought.
咱们就别跟他们客气了
Well, I'd say we pulled the band aid.
嗯  不过诉讼是个问题
Yeah. The, uh, lawsuits are a concern, though.
我们在他们的保留地铺设了一条管道
We put a pipeline through their reservation,
陆军工程兵团也参与了
and we did it with the Army Corps of Engineers.
俗话说大到不能倒
They talk about being too big to fail,
说的就是我们
they're talking about us.
州长  杰米  我走了
Governor. Jamie.
好吧
Well...
挺难受的吧
That must have been difficult.
也没有
Not really.
总有一天他会明白的
Well, one day he'll see.
他会知道你这么做是为了他
He's gonna know that you did this for him.
不  我不是
No, I didn't.
以后不是了
Not anymore.
从现在开始  我做的只是为了我自己
From now on, what I do is for me.
靠  我把发油落在旅行包里了
Oh, shit, I forgot my, uh, Show Sheen in my groom bag.
我去拿
I can grab it.
吉米  你康复了吗
Hey, Jimmy, you all healed up?
嗯  快了
Yeah, we're getting there.
什么时候回来比赛
When you gonna be back on the circuit?
医生说我不能再骑烈马了
Doc said I'm not supposed to ride anymore.
吉米  医生跟我们所有人都说过
Shit, Jimmy. Doc has told us all that before.
你要退出牛仔竞技吗
Are you quitting rodeo?
达顿先生说我不应该
Mr. Dutton told me I'm not supposed--
达顿先生  就是给你打了烙印的
Mr. Dutton, he's the one who stuck you with that hot iron.
那个达顿先生吗
That Mr. Dutton?
我不想在轮椅上度过余生
I don't want to live the rest of my life in a wheelchair.
那就不要啊
Then don't.
即使你残了  过来  转身
Even if you do, come here. Turn around.
加油啊  安伯雷
Give it hell, Amberley.
那还用你说么
That's all I ever give it.
她腰部以下瘫痪了
She's paralyzed from the waist down,
但她赢我的次数
and she has whipped me more times
我已经数不清了
than I can remember.
你参加牛仔竞技时  我看到你非常开心
When I saw you rodeo, I saw a really happy man.
你愿意冒着生命危险去做爱做的事
I saw a man who risked his life to do what he loved.
然后我爱上了你
And I fell in love with him.
爷们点  你就可以拥有我
Be that man and you can have me.
像你现在这样嘛  到时候再说吧
But be this one, and I'll see ya later.
我很害怕
Hey, I'm scared.
我他妈
I'm fucking...
我他妈很害怕
I'm fucking scared.
谁不害怕呢
Who ain't scared?
我每次比赛都很害怕
Hell, I'm scared every time I run out there.
但我是牛仔  还是完赛了啊
but I cowboy the fuck up and I do it anyway.
如果你如此渴望追求归属感
If you're so desperate to belong to something,
那就做我的男人吧
then belong to me,
我们可以参加全国的牛仔竞技
and we can rodeo our way across this whole damn country.
这就是你的归属感
Belong to that.
但是不要成为有钱人的牲口
But don't be one of that rich man's cattle.
好的
Okay.
很好
Good.
去拿我的旅行包吧
Now go get my groom bag.
我离开的样子很性感吧
I look pretty good leaving, don't I?
确实
Pretty good.
真的很性感
Naw, really good.
你有一个窗口
You have a window, you know.
什么窗口
A window to what?
在一个充满敌人的房间里  你看起来像他的朋友
In a room full of his enemies, you look like his friend.
但你不是他的朋友
But you're not his friend.
嗯  我不是
No, I'm not.
你有机会从他手上解救那片土地
You have an opportunity to free that land of him.
谁也看不出来是你干的
And it will look like everyone but you who did it.
我不是罪犯
I'm not a criminal.
这只是他们的法律
It's only a crime by their laws.
我们的法律超越了冰河时代  这是我们的责任
By our laws, which have outlasted an ice age, it is duty.
保护我们的土地和我们的生活方式
To protect our land and preserve our way of life.
这是信仰
It is religion.
难道你相信他们的信仰吗
Or did you buy into their religion
毕竟你接受了他们的法律
when you bought into their laws?
我会用他们的规则打败他们
I will beat them with their own rules.
规则就是用来打破的
They make their rules to be broken.
美国违反了自己制定的每一条规则
The United States has broken every rule it has ever made.
与法国的第一个条约  以及与我们的每一个条约
From its first treaty with France to every treaty with us,
与伊朗签订的最后一个条约
to their last treaty with Iran.
他们只要求别人遵守他们的规则
They only hold others to their rules.
他们想打就打  想打哪儿就打哪
They make war when they want, where they want,
想要什么就抢什么
they take what they want,
然后制定规则来阻止别人拿回去
then make rules that keep you from taking it back.
他们为奴隶制定规则
They make rules for the slave
也为主人制定规则
and they make rules for the masters.
你在遵守奴隶的规则
You're following the slave rules.
但如果你遵循主人的规则
But if you follow the masters' rules,
那你就会杀了他  夺回我们的土地
then you'll kill him, and give us our land back.
你和一个武士部落的人同行
You travel with a man from a warrior clan,
但你不让他发动战争
but you do not let him make war.
你让他也变成了奴隶
You make him a slave, too.
也许你已经听够了  做事不需要得到许可
Maybe you've heard enough that you don't ask permission.
也许你可以为我们的人民开战
Maybe you go and make war for our people.
然后我们就可以回家了
And then... we go home.
蒙大拿畜牧协会
畜牧协会主席在你办公室
Chairmen of the Stockgrower's Association are in your office.
-哪一个  -所有人
- Which one? - All of them.
你们怎么样
How you boys doing?
有你在就更好了
Better, with you in office.
好吧  谢谢
Oh, well... Appreciate that.
不  是我们该谢谢你
No, we appreciate it.
我能帮什么忙吗
How can I help you?
我们在想  也许我们可以帮助你
Well, we're thinking maybe... maybe we can help you.
在这个过程中  也可以帮助我们自己
And help ourselves in the process.
州长只剩两年任期了
Governor's termed out. She's got two years left.
现在是决定谁接替她的时候了
Time to decide who replaces her is now.
我们想推荐你  凯斯
We're thinking that's... that's you, Kayce.
我们是认真的
Hey, we're serious.
我不是政客
I ain't no politician.
说的没错
You're damn right, you aren't.
你坦诚直白  言出必行
You say what you mean and you do what you say.
蒙大拿州又不一定认可我的正义观
I'm not sure my brand of justice is what this state wants.
这正是本州急需的品质
It's exactly what this state wants and needs.
有个混蛋偷你的牛
Some bastard goes and steals your cattle,
你没找治安官
you don't punt it to the sheriff,
而是直接去杀了那狗娘养的
you just go over there and shoot the son of a bitch.
这算什么竞选口号啊
I don't think that's much of a campaign slogan.
孩子  你可以在T恤上印个"我杀了一个偷牛贼"
Hell, son. You could print "I killed a cattle thief"
然后拿到教堂去卖
on t-shirts and sell 'em in church.
不行了  时代变了
Not anymore. Times have changed.
也许吧  但蒙大拿州没有变
Maybe so. But Montana hasn't.
博兹曼  米苏拉选不了州长
Bozeman, Missoula, they don't decide the Governor.
大瀑布城  迪伦  迈耳才能选
Great Falls decides. Dillon decides. Miles City decides.
那些嬉皮士肯定会抱怨和抗议
Those hippies will bitch and protest
然后发推说他们不还学校贷款了
and Twitter out bullshit about not paying off their school loans,
但他们投不了票
but they won't vote.
只要雪道上还有雪
They're not gonna stand in line and put their money
他们就没办法排队投票
where their mouth is when there's snow on the ski slopes.
他们五月举行选举  我们就玩完了
They start holding elections in May, we're fucked.
但在那之前  将由我们决定谁来管理这个州
But until then, we decide who runs this state.
凯斯  这需要时间
Kayce, these things take time.
是时候计划了  想想吧
Time to plan. Think about it.
当人们离开房间时  州长不用站起来
Governors don't have to stand when people leave the room.
坐着握手就好
You just sit there and shake hands.
保重
Take care.
董事会准备好了我们就开会
When the board is ready we'll conference in,
但你要向他们解释  这是一个恶作剧
but explain to them: this is a hatchet job.
举报人甚至都不是员工
Okay, the caller isn't even an employee.
你怎么知道  举报人是匿名的
How can you know that? The caller is anonymous.
她看着我的眼睛  亲口承认了
She looked me in the fucking eye and told me it was her!
应该雇佣她  而不是解雇她的
Should have hired her instead of firing her.
你能回避一下吗
Can you give us a minute?
好的
Okay.
你得玩阴的了
You need to start playing dirty.
我一直在玩阴的  然后他们阴了我们
I've been playing dirty. They play dirty right back.
他们在玩零和游戏
They are playing a zero sum game,
还拿我的事业做赌注
they're doing it with my fucking career.
这绝对不行
I will not have it.
这不像蒙大拿州的土地交易吧
Don't feel much like a land deal in Montana, does it?
嗯  感觉像也门的石油交易
No. It feels like an oil deal in Yemen.
从现在开始  我们就要这样对待
And from now on, that's how we treat it.
你可以吗
Can you do that?
你说什么就是什么
I can do whatever you want.
爆胎了吗
Got a flat?
是的  我想叫拖车
Yeah, I'm trying to call a tow truck,
但是没信号
but I don't have any signal.
你有备用的吗
You got a spare?
我不知道  这是租来的车
I don't know. It's a rental.
打开看看吧
Let's open her, find out.
猜猜我多大了
Guess how old I am.
八岁
Eight.
这不是我第一次猜了  孩子
Not my first rodeo, son.
看  所有的装备都在这里
Look. You got the whole kit right here.
我没有钱
I... I don't have any money.
我只是想说  我没有什么可以给你的
I'm just saying... I don't have anything to give you.
女士  你从哪里来
Ma'am, where are you from?
恩西诺  在加州
Encino. That's in California.
我知道恩西诺在哪里
I know where Encino is.
在这里  只要是对的事我们就会去做
Out here, we do things because they're the right thing to do
这是我们唯一的理由
and that's the only reason we need.
你想学生活技能吗
You wanna learn a life skill?
什么是生活技能
What's a life skill?
让你不用站在路边
It's something that'll keep you from standing
等手机信号的技能
on the side of the road hoping for a phone signal.
听起来很方便啊
Sounds handy.
以及如何
And how...
没想到这种事我还会帮你第二次
Never thought I'd have to do this for you again.
我也是
Yeah. Me neither.
她看起来有多糟糕  特里
How bad is she gonna look, Terry?
很难说
Well, it's hard to say.
要看防腐工行不行了
Depends on how good the embalmer was.
如果防腐得好  那
If he was good, then, uh,
她可能会看起来像我们埋葬她的时候
she might look like she did when we buried her.
但如果不好  那
But if he wasn't, then, uh...
可能会很糟糕
It could be bad.
希望是艾迪做的防腐处理
Let's just hope Eddie did the embalming.
嗯  是埃迪
Yeah. Yeah, it was Eddie.
妈妈
Hey, Mama.
我遇到了一个人
I met somebody.
我要和她共度余生
I'm gonna spend the rest of my life with her.
我可以去商店
I could have gone to some store
给她买个傻逼戒指
and bought her some fucking ring,
但这有什么意思呢
but what does that mean?
妈的  对不起
Shit, I'm sorry.
不该说脏话的
Shouldn't curse.
我想让她戴你的戒指
I want her to wear yours.
你可以
Maybe you can, uh...
你也可以稍微了解一下她
Maybe you can know her a little too, somehow.
我不知道
I don't know...
我爱你  妈妈
I love you, Mama.
谢谢
Thank you.
来  过来
Come on. Come on.
过来
Come on around.
好了  好了
All right there, right there.
从马上摔下来  就再骑上去
You fall off the horse, you just get back on.
不喜欢吗
Don't like that, huh?
好好弓几次背  我就放了你
Just give me a couple good bucks and I'll let it loose.
来吧
Come on.
舒瓦茨和梅耶
你想从供应室拿点什么吗
Do you want anything from the supply room?
是的  我要笔  铅笔  纸
Uh, yes. I want the pens, the pencils, the paper,
咖啡  奶壶  都拿走
the coffee, the creamer... we're taking everything.
-我全都要  -已经确认威拉·海斯总裁
- I want it all. - ...has confirmed that CEO Willa Hayes
将被安排休假
will be placed on leave
直到独立调查结束
until after an independent investigation has been conducted.
海斯被指控为以下引述
Hayes was accused of what is being called and I quote,
"工作场所不当行为"
"workplace misconduct."
海斯小姐和她的律师
Miss Hayes and her lawyers were unavailable
不会对任何评论做出回应
for any type of comment...
这个放你车里吗
Do you want this in your car?
那不是我的
Oh, that's not mine.
是寄给你的
It's addressed to you.
奇怪  盒子里还有个盒子
Weird. A box within a box.
等等  我不知道那是什么
Wait, I don't know what that is.
不要
Don't--
我不是说我会参加竞选
I'm not saying I'm gonna do it,
我只是在跟你说他们说了什么
I was just telling you what they said.
过去三年你所做的一切
Everything you've been doing for the past three years
都是你说你不想做的事
is something you said you didn't want to do...
可你还是去做了
And now you just keep doing it.
好吧  那我不跟你说我的日常了
Fine, I just won't tell you what happens during my day
到时候秘密会越来越多
and the secrets can grow and grow.
凯斯
Kayce?
Kayce!
好了
Alright, now.
把螺母给我
Go hand me them lug nuts.
我不知道去哪了
I don't know where they are.
伙计
Buddy.
这是你唯一的工作
That was your only job.
我小便时把它们放下了
I set them down when I pee'd.
这不是有线索了么  你在哪里小便的
Now we're getting somewhere. Where'd you do that?
好  去找找吧
All right. Go hunt 'em up.
谢谢你的帮助
Thank you for helping.
这是人们应该做的  不是吗
It's what people are supposed to do, isn't it?
但他们没有
But they don't.
有些人是没有
Some don't.
不用了
No.
我们搞定了  谢谢你停车
We got it figured, thanks for stopping.
你是约翰·杜顿吧
Hey, you're John Dutton, aren't you?
是的
Yep.
您的呼叫已转接到自动语音留言
Your call has been forwarded to an automatic voice message--
喂
Hello.
杰米  我一个人都联系不上
Jamie, hey. I can't find anybody.
贝丝  你爸和凯斯都联系不上
Not Beth, not your dad, not Kayce. Nobody.
里普  你不应该再给我打电话了
Rip, I don't think you should call me anymore.
该死
Damn it, hey!
滚出去
Get the fuck out of here!
走开  走开
Go on, get!
Go on! Hey! Go! Hey!
快滚  滚出去  混蛋
Go on, get the fuck out of here, you piece of shit.
该死
Goddamn.
我不喜欢朝马开枪
I hate shooting horses.
放松  放松
Easy, easy.
放松
Easy, boy.
我宁愿杀一千人也不愿意杀一匹马
I'd rather kill a thousand men than shoot another horse.
现在你们可以吃它了
Now you can fucking eat him!
今天整个山谷都死气沉沉的
Whole fucking valley's dying today.
意料之外  情理之中
Doesn't that fucking figure.